Hey everybody, thanks for listening to
the Grow Your Life podcast. My name is
Jeremiah Growski. In this podcast, I
talk about ways for you to grow in your
life, in your business to make more
money, scale your business, and reach
your goals. Now, I talk about my story
all the time at the beginning of all my
YouTube videos, my successes. Built
multiple online coaching, online course
businesses to over eight figures. It's
over $10 million a year.
and I can help you reach your goals
making six figures, seven figures, eight
figures. But I want to talk about in
kind of more of a traditional podcast
form. It's going to be a little bit more
relaxed, down to
earth
is my
story and where I've come from and the
lessons that I've learned along the way.
There's going to be lessons for you to
glean from this. nothing boring that you
don't care
about. Uh but also some stuff that might
be intriguing as well to you. So again,
my story in business, very interesting.
Um grew up had a mom. Some of you all
know who my mom is. Sandy
Kowski, who uh actually built an online
business
um back before Amazon was even built.
She built an e-commerce store. And
so in a sense, in a very real sense,
um
I come from a
family with a lot of success in internet
business, e-commerce, and online
sales. And it started with my mom who
made millions online before Amazon was
even around
um in the 90s.
So, like we're looking at over 30 years
ago. Incredible.
Okay. Now, I wasn't old enough to even
know anything about business back then.
I got my start helping her with that,
but I learned stuff along the way. My
business
story starts when
I
turned Oh, I was 16 at the time, but I
had I had met a it was a company. My mom
went to this seminar and it was a sales
seminar. The person putting it on's name
was Danny
Johnson and it was interesting, I will
say.
Um, I'm not afraid to say it. I'm not a
not a huge fan anymore of of Danny. Um,
kind of got a bit of a sour taste in my
mouth after years of being closely
connected with them. But for years, I
worked uh with them, worked for
Danny, helped add a lot to their bottom
line uh from a marketing perspective.
Um, and I got my start creating and
editing CD and DV products. I was super
into video editing before it was like a
trend. Interestingly enough, kind of the
same way I am, I'm always like five
years early on a lot of the stuff that
everybody's going to learn about. Like I
was using AI back in 2021, like
crazy. I know a lot about AI, a lot more
than most people now when it comes to
building your business. I was doing
video stuff back when like nobody knew
about video. Um I I wanted to be a
filmmaker at the time and so I would
edit all these like crazy things
together and all that that kind of
stuff. That's where I got my
start cuz then I went and worked with
Danny and helped create the CD and the
DVD products that uh she sold by editing
them all together, putting it all
together um and that. But again because
I came from this
background of
business, I was always having ideas,
sharing the ideas. I would always speak
up in meetings. I didn't really know
that you weren't supposed to speak up in
meetings. Nobody told me that.
Um, so I'm like this like kid who just
every meeting I would speak up and share
ideas and a lot of those ideas were
pretty good. They're they're pretty
valuable.
Um, fast forward to I was about 19 years
old and I started to do some dabbling in
affiliate marketing. It was really like
a weird
dabbling like in like in the weirdest
sense. So I
uh I got a taste for drinking alcohol
quite a bit around the time and as well
for about a year or two, this is kind of
a dark part of my story.
Um experimented a little bit with like
uh prescription opiates. Not like a lot,
but like Vicodin
and again like I would not recommend
this to anybody, but yeah, some drug
usage. Um,
and I I'd have all these ideas for
business while I was doing this. So,
this wired my brain in a very weird way
that took me years to unwire
um to where like now, you know, I I have
not used anything including alcohol. I
don't even drink caffeine. I haven't
drank caffeine in over a year.
Um and but I haven't had alcohol in it's
almost been now four years. And
so that was not where I was at at the
time. Like that was like alcohol was a
big part of my life and all that, but I
was like I was using it because I didn't
feel safe to come up with and share
ideas. And so that's one of the first
lessons I want to share with you is that
for
me, I've always chased after where does
my highest creativity come from.
I'm always looking for the edge of my
creativity.
And of course, the alcohol and the pills
helped because it helped me get out of
my head and into that creative flow
state. And I want you to think about
like musicians and artists that have
done this over the years. What I learned
now through therapy and healing and
learning how to calm my nervous system
down on
demand, learning how to listen to my
inner
voice is that my creativity comes when
my nervous system feels
safe. And I call it the the big three,
feeling unstoppable,
unshakable, and safe.
and and and and really like that's what
I would feel when I would drink alcohol.
I would
feel this enormous that's why they call
it liquid courage,
right? So, what I've done is I've been
able to cultivate in myself without
needing to use substance because I I
knew people who could do it, but I was
like, how do you do
this? I couldn't do it. And I had to
learn like, okay, how do I cultivate
that? So, that's one of the first things
I'll tell you is you totally can rewire
your brain to your your best level of
creativity, flow state. Um, like I even
when I first started this podcast, I
would take a shot of tequila to even
record the podcast. So, again, I don't
drink alcohol anymore. Um, I am actually
very proud of that fact and I'm not
going to.
Um, from
there, all that to say, I, you know, I
made some really dumb choices. And it
was interesting because I made
$750,000 in affiliate
marketing one year and then almost the
next year I think I made like maybe less
than like under
$10,000 and I had like a little bit of
savings and some investment stuff that I
was able to sell to take care of certain
things,
But I was miserable. My life was
miserable.
And I hit rock bottom. That's when I
first moved to Austin, Texas. I live
here in Austin, Texas now. Um, but the
first time that I moved to Austin, Texas
was during that time. I became a DJ. I
used my marketing chops that I knew and
we were marketing nightclub events here
in Austin. And that was crazy because we
would get a lot of people to show up to
our our events with a lot of the
marketing things that I knew how to do.
So that was kind of incredible to put
all together um to see that to see that
happen. I don't regret that at all.
Again, that ties back into the alcohol
consumption, all that cuz I was in that
this party season right there.
Um but then my business
career takes a transition where
um and again I'm so grateful to my
mom. She saw that I had hit rock bottom
and she had offered me a job to help run
her marketing. So I was I was fired from
Danny Johnson uh because of these
alcohol issues that I had.
um made some really dumb
choices and it it was affecting my life
in a lot of ways. I hit rock bottom and
then mom was going to give me a a a hand
up and I'm so grateful for that for her
giving me that opportunity. And what
ended up happening was
um I
discovered for the first time what it
meant to take care of
myself, what it meant to love myself,
what a sense of self-love meant. I
didn't know it at the time that's what
it
was, but I had focused on my my health
and fitness at the time. I went on this
crazy fitness journey where I lost like
pounds. Um, well, no, I lo I lost 100
pounds, not 150 pounds. I got down to um
I think it was I got down to 150 pounds.
Yes. And I had I had abs six-pack for
the first time. It's like whoa, it's
crazy. It's awesome. you know, but I was
like killing myself in the gym all the
time for that. Um, and
then after
that, I met my now
wife and my whole life changed. Got
flipped on its head. Met a beautiful
woman. Just like everything I could have
ever dreamed of or imagined in a woman,
she had.
and in in
in her personality and how she looked,
everything was just like
amazing. And so like I was like, "This
is awesome." We didn't get married right
away. Um I was again working with my
mom. I kind of decided to get my life a
little bit in order at the time when I
met her. This was my first instance of
finding something that was similar to
therapy, but it wasn't really therapy.
Um, it was like it was kind of like talk
therapy, but it like mixed with some
religious stuff that I did. And it
radically changed the way that I was
thinking. And I can look back now, it's
because it gave me a sense of safety for
a brief period of time. And in that when
I felt that sense of safety, there was a
lot of synchronicities that started to
happen. And there's a lot of
amazing things that came together in my
life that then you know our mind and our
body seeks
homeostasis. Meaning that it will return
back to what it believes it deserves
like a like a
thermometer. The temperature goes up,
you turn the temperature down, it
returns back to the what the setting is.
So I met uh I met Abigail, my now wife.
I had gone through this. I had felt
super confident, amazing. And then I had
started to like lose that confidence. I
started to go back to where I was
uh mentally and that was really hard for
me because I had experienced something
that now like I know how to cultivate. I
know in my entire life how I live my
life is literally based around that. I
felt what I feel today in living my life
that that gives me joy and pleasure and
and it's amazing about how I understand
about the mind and mindset and and
managing my thoughts. I had discovered
this during that sort of religious
experience for the first
time and that's when I met my wife
because I had the confidence uh to go
out there and do that and it was and and
it was amazing and I and I truly believe
like she was she was exactly who the
Lord God had planned for me. It's an
awesome. So anyways, I digress from
there.
is we started building my mom's
business. I was working with my mom. My
wife was working with my mom. She was
not my wife at the time.
Um, and we helped grow that business to
over $10 million a
year. No, sorry, $20 million a year.
That one was 20 million. $20 million a
year. The next one was 10 million. And
so my
journey was in
business 22 years. It's been 22 years
when I started working with Danny
Johnson. I started on this
journey in this industry, the coaching
and online course industry and then
dabbled in the affiliate marketing and
then marketing of live events with the
DJ events. And then I started working
with my mom, working for her, doing the
marketing. But then when I met my wife,
which was in 2014, so we're looking at
like 11 years ago. So the like the first
11 of those 22 years
um was just me kind of like after I left
home after being homeschooled finding
myself. The last 11 years has been
really dialed in in
creating millions of dollars of wealth
uh strategically for the companies that
I've worked with and then for myself and
my own company.
um you know and and about about two
years ago for the first time one of my
own businesses made seven figures hit a
million dollars. Um, I have not earned
less
than a quarter million
dollars
since oh
gosh, I would say since 2020 2016
uh 2017, like around then. So, for at
least the last eight or nine years, I
haven't earned less than a quarter
million dollars. And for most of those
years, for about seven of those years,
has been in my own business. So that's
really cool. And I think that that's a
that's a testament to
like that's my baseline minimum. And I
know how to get people to a quarter
million dollars from zero. I know what
it takes to do that. I know without a
doubt, if you're following me, if you're
watching me, you want to be making a
quarter million dollars. I know how to
get you there. I know what it takes. I
know what the mental game is to get
there. I know the sacrifices you got to
make. And that's what I mentor people on
all the time in my wealthy coach academy
programs is how to do that. Okay. So,
from there, we had helped my mom uh
scale her business to over $20
million. And then
um it was interesting. My mom and
I got like kind of toxically entwined
intertwined in our
relationship. Like what I mean by that
is
just not in a healthy way both in
business and personal relationship. And
so we ended up kind of parting ways and
I didn't even really talk with my mom
that much for a couple of years.
This was right after I got married, by
the way. So, my life got shaken up, got
married, and then my mom and I parted
ways and I started my own business. And
so, this is back in
2018. Um, you know, and things were
things are were going well. Um, during
that time, I got a chance to work with a
ton of different organizations. I took
the skills that I learned working with
my mom and building that to then helping
do like over a dozen
um a lot of them were spiritual leaders
reached audiences of people uh growing
in my own personal development during
that time. And one of those was one of
my friends Rick Pino. My wife and I
ended up
working most of our time with his
business and we helped him scale that to
over $10
million. Um, it's called Worship Coach.
So, it was right alongside him. We were
able to build that. I talked a lot of
examples during that that time period.
And that was up until
2022. That was three years
ago. Um, in
2022 then my mom and I started working
together again. I helped her
um scale. She started trading stocks,
helped her scale that coaching business
and launched my own coaching program in
2022. All during that
time, my coaching program then within a
year hit seven figures. Uh our best
month, I did over $160,000 in cash
received sales. This is the best month
I'd ever had in business, period.
Um and and so the lessons that I had
learned along the
way are this that a everything in
life leads
us at the right place at the right time.
God is never late. He's on time if we
accept it. If we stop trying to control
things, we learn to surrender to lead us
to the right time, the right moment in
time in our life to do amazing,
incredible things that we're called
to. And so then for me, what I found was
I was able to take these skills that I
had learned over the years, build my
coaching business, build my coaching
program, and then share those skills
with other people. And that's what I do
every single day right now.
is if you're a coach, if you're a course
creator, you want to know how do I get
more clients
online, I can help you do that. I can
show you exactly what strategies are
working right
now. I can show you exactly how to
structure things, how to build your
marketing campaigns, your advertising
campaigns, your funnels, your lead
magnets, all of that. And that's what I
do in my coaching program. I also do
some highlevel consulting as
well where I could actually come into
your business and build that with you.
It's not it's not cheap. Uh but for the
right person, it's worth it 100%. To
work with me, to be able to build that
with you and to come alongside you and
to create those
results. And so, listen, if you're
looking to do that, you want to work
with me, whether it be inside of my
Wealthy Coach Academy
program, you go find that over my
website. There should be a link in the
bio as well. You can go check that out.
Or you want to work with me in
consulting, you go write me on
Instagram and I can schedule a call with
you where we can talk about that. And I
and and before I do any like highle
consulting, I definitely will get on a
call with somebody. Um, but I only I
only work with a select group of people
doing that every year just because of
the capacity and the effort and what I
do in that. And so again, if I think
you're qualified, if I think you kind of
fit into
that, then I would schedule a call with
you to help you accomplish that. So
again, that's my story thus far.
Um, a little bit of like personal
life. Massive shift that's happened. I
got a picture right
here. My wife gave birth. We got two
sons. Kirn is the little one. Luca or
not Luca. Luca is my nephew. Kairen and
Holston right
here are my
sons. And that's changed my life. That's
completely and radically changed my
life. who I am, my my
personality. I've become more of the man
that I've always wanted to
be. And I couldn't be more grateful. And
I can tell you this that going off of
alcohol, I was using I used to use CBD
oil every day.
Um going off of
caffeine has helped me be able to hear
my inner voice and become a better
parent and dad.
to my kids and a better business leader.
And so again, if I can encourage you in
one thing is learn, do the
work to where you're not mentally
self-sabotaging
yourself every single
day. It's worth it.
And if this episode has helped you or
anything or you found some value in it,
please share it with somebody. Don't
keep this information to yourself. I
know you know somebody who could use
this lesson and some of the lessons that
I've shared from this and I'd love to
see them as well. All right, everybody.
Grow your life. We'll talk soon. Have a
good one.
[Music]